Our religions have given us definitions
of success. Our pop culture economics
have all given definitions of success
that are partial at best, if not
completely broken. And the people who
succeeded those definitions are in the
process of their success the cause of a
lot of harm in the world. And so really
waking up to what is a way to be able to
have what I really want occur. And what I
really want is both my self
actualization and me getting to touch
the world in a way that really
profoundly changes the world for the
better because everything that I get
dies with me but the way that I touch
the world continues on forever. So the
invitation is to join us in really
inquiring into a definition of success
that's meaningful for everyone, the
unique expression for you and then
actually really living that.